(Sheldon:)In.
(Sheldon:)Let me guess.
(Voice:)And out.
(Sheldon:)What was I gonna do?
Two "ins" in a row?
(Sheldon:)-Where's my lemonade?
-I didn't get it.
(Sheldon:)A fitting swan song
to your career as a waitress
(Sheldon:)to forget my order one last time.
(Penny:)Do you think quitting
my job was a mistake?
(Sheldon:)Do you see me drinking lemonade?
(Penny:)No. I'm serious.
(Sheldon:)Why do you ask?
(Penny:)Because Leonard just pissed me off.
(Penny:)Am I being an idiot or not?
(Sheldon:)No, I don't think you are.
(Stuart:)Really?
(Sheldon:)The best way to achieve
a goal is to devote 100 percent
(Sheldon:)of your time and energy to it.
(Sheldon:)When I decided I was
going to be a physicist,
(Sheldon:)I didn't take some other job
in case it didn't work out.
(Sheldon:)Which wasn't easy because
there was a lot of pressure